

CONTACT ME

- +389 71 342 119
- petro19986@gmail.com

http://linkedin.com/in/anastasija-petrovska-496759278

UI. Via Egnatia 4, Gjorche Petrov, Skopje, Macedonia

EDUCATION

High School graduate SUGS Orce Nikolov 2013 - 2017

Faculty of Economics
Bachelor Degree of E-business
Ss. Cyril and Methodius University,
Skopje, Macedonia
2017 - 2022

SKILLS

- Customer Service
- Communication
- Adaptability
- Good Team Leader
- Fast Learner
- Creative Thinking
- Organization
- MS Office tools

LANGUAGES

- Knowledge of English language
- Knowledge of German language

Anastasija Petrovska

Assistant Manager

WORK EXPERIENCE

MPG Solutions I Skopje, Macedonia 2018 (3 mos)

Promotions and active sales of products

Food Bar Trend I Skopje, Macedonia 2019 (4 mos)

Serving customers

Burger King I Hamburg, Germany

2019 (3 mos)

- Greeting guests with a smile, receiving orders
- Preparing and packaging food and drink products
- Processing payments
- Responds appropriately to customer issues
- Working with others to achieve team goals

Stradivarius, Zara, Massimo Dutti, Inditex I Skopje, Macedonia

Sales assistant and cashier

2020 - 2022(2y, 3mos)

- Ensuring high levels of customer satisfaction through excellent sales service
- Maintaining outstanding store condition and visual merchandising standards
- Assist with the sales process by maintaining a fully stocked store
- Offer product, promotion, and pricing information by exploring customer requests
- Process transactions

Massimo Dutti, Inditex I Skopje, Macedonia

2023 - Present

Assistant Manager (Responsible)

- Making sure that the entire team complies with the standards established by the ompany when advising
- Ensuring that the store maintains the standards of the company's image
- Complies with merchandise management processes in the store and storage areas
- Analysis and business decision making
- Maintaining the administration of human resources
- Training and providing information to the team
- Designing work schedules and report writing

SUMMARY

Dedicated, ambitious, hard-working Economics graduate willing to improve and grow. Have 3+ years of experience in customer service and familiarity with a retail store management. With great desire to prove and provide my skills and advance my career in a growth-oriented, dynamic work environment.